

Telefon:

+90 539 647 32 46

Email:

alicanbayazit300@gmail.com

GitHub:

https://github.com/Bayazzitt

Adres:

Istanbul/Zeytinburnu

Ali Can BAYAZIT

Hakkımda

Tasarım ve kodlama üzerine 1 yıldır çalışmalar yapıyorum. Patika.dev'den almış olduğum eğitimi bireysel çalışmalarım ve eğitimler ile destekleyerek kendimi Front-End alanında her geçen gün daha da geliştiriyorum. Araştıran, analitik düşünüp devamlı öğrenen ve sektör değişikliğinde cesur kararlar alıp, bilişim ve gümrükleme sektöründen edindiğim tecrübe ile müşteri ilişkilerine hakim, çözüm odaklı bir geliştiriciyim.

Beceriler

- HTML
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRİPT
- REACT
- GOOGLE FIREBASE
- MODERN UI/UX DESIGN

Diller

- İngilizce

İş Deneyimi

IT Uzmanı

Kozmoklinik | 2022 - 2022

- Server sistem yönetimi ve donanım hakkında tecrübe sahibi

İthalat Operasyon Uzmanı

Emin Gümrük Müşavirliği | 2019 - 2021

- İthalat ve nakliye işlemlerinin tüm operasyonel süreçlerinin sorunsuz bir şekilde takip etmek, yürütmek ve sonuçlandırmak.
- Gümrükleme programı (Evrim) kullanarak iş akışını kontrol etmek.

Eğitim

Anadolu Üniversitesi

Uluslararası Ticaret | 2018-2020

İstanbul Aydın Üniversitesi

Dış Ticaret | Tam Burslu | 2016-2018

Lisans / Sertifika

- Patika Front-End Web Development
- Udemy Uctan Uca React (Storybook, Webpack, Tailwind, Jest)
- İstanbul Aydın Üniversitesi İnsansız Hava Aracı Ticari Pilot Lisansı (İHA-I)



Mobile:

+90 539 647 32 46

Email:

alicanbayazit300@gmail.com

GitHub:

https://github.com/Bayazzitt

Address:

Istanbul/Zeytinburnu

Ali Can BAYAZIT

About Me

I have been working on design and coding for 1 year. By supporting the training I received from Patika.dev with my individual studies and trainings, I am improving myself in the field of Front-End day by day. I am a solution-oriented developer who researches, thinks analytically, constantly learns, takes courageous decisions in changing the sector, and has a command of customer relations with the experience I gained from the IT and customs sector.

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT
- GOOGLE FIREBASE
- MODERN UI/UX DESIGN

Languages

- English
- Turkish

Work Experience

IT Specialist

Kozmoklinik | 2022 - 2022

- Experinced in server system management and hardware

Import Operation Specialist

Emin Gümrük Müşavirliği | 2019 - 2021

- To follow, carry out and conclude all operational processes of import and transportation transactions without any problems.
- To follow up the work using the customs clearance program (Evrim).

Academic History

Anadolu University

Uluslararası Ticaret | 2018-2020

İstanbul Aydın University

Dış Ticaret | Full Scholarship | 2016-2018

License / Certificate

- Patika Front-End Web Development
- Udemy End-to-End React (Storybook, Webpack, Tailwind, Jest)
- Commercial Pilot License (UAV-I)